Guide to the Montana Statehood Centennial Commission and Office Records 1982-1991
Montana Historical Society
- Subject Files
  - Northwest Centennial: Documents West Project, 1988-1990 (Box-folder 12 / 18)
  - Northwest Centennial: Idaho, 1986-1990 (Box-folder 12 / 19)
  - Northwest Centennial: North Dakota, 1985-1989 (Box-folder 12 / 20-21)
  - Northwest Centennial: South Dakota, 1985-1989 (Box-folder 12 / 22)
  - Northwest Centennial: "Voyage of the Centennial Messenger" (school exercises to celebrate centennial in six-state region), 1988-1989 (Box-folder 12 / 23)
  - Northwest Centennial: Washington, 1983-1989 (Box-folder 12 / 24-26)
  - Northwest Centennial: Wyoming, 1985-1990 (Box-folder 12 / 27)
  - Office inventory, 1988 (Box-folder 12 / 28)
  - Other states: Arkansas Sesquicentennial, 1986 (Box-folder 12 / 29)
  - Other states: Bicentennial of the U.S. Constitution, 1986-1988 (Box-folder 12 / 30-31)
  - Other states: Bicentennial of the U.S. Constitution, 1986-1988 (Box-folder 13 / 1)
  - Other states: Colorado Centennial / Bicentennial final report, 1976 (Box-folder 13 / 2)
  - Other states: Michigan Sesquicentennial report, 1987 (Box-folder 13 / 3)
  - Other states: Tennessee Homecoming '86, 1986 (Box-folder 13 / 4)
  - Other states: Texas Sesquicentennial commemorative products list, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 13 / 5)
  - Other states: Virginia Cultural Laureate Awards, 1977-1981 (Box-folder 13 / 6)
  - Other states: miscellaneous, 1983-1990 (Box-folder 13 / 7)
  - Parades, 1989 (Box-folder 13 / 8)
  - "A Passion for Peace" (Nadine Arlyn portrayal of Jeannette Rankin), 1987-1989 (Box-folder 13 / 9)
  - "Pillars of the Past" (St. John's Home Foundation), 1989 (Box-folder 13 / 10)
  - President George Bush visit [photos], 1989 (Box-folder 13 / 11)
  - Proclamation of statehood [photocopy], 1889 (Box-folder 13 / 12)
  - Proclamations and resolutions, 1987-1989 (Box-folder 13 / 13)
  - Product and project proposals, 1984-1989 (Box-folder 13 / 14)
  - Products (approvals), 1987 (Box-folder 13 / 15)
  - Projects: Blackfeet Country, by Pat Lawshe (re planned tourist brochures), 1986-1989 (Box-folder 13 / 16)
  - Projects: Eureka Community Hall, 1986-1989 (Box-folder 13 / 17)
  - Projects: Music in Montana (re planned history of music in Montana), 1986 (Box-folder 13 / 18)
  - Proposals: Montana Carriage Company, 1986 (Box-folder 13 / 19)
  - Proposals: Mountain Visions (re planned slide shows), 1984-1986 (Box-folder 13 / 20)
  - Proposals: Rolf Olson, Montana Outdoor Leadership Expedition video, 1983 (Box-folder 13 / 21)
  - Proposals: PS, a Partnership (Linda Peavy and Ursula Smith production of opera Pamelia), 1984-1987 (Box-folder 13 / 22)
  - Proposals: Jo Ann Rachele, Folklife Festival, 1985 (Box-folder 13 / 23)
  - Proposals: Mona Vanek (history of Noxon), 1985-1987 (Box-folder 13 / 24)
  - Proposals: Paul Wilson (Montana Atlas), 1985 (Box-folder 13 / 25)
  - Red Lodge Grizzly Peak-a-Boos (can-can dancers), 1987 (Box-folder 13 / 26)
  - Red Lodge Mountain Man Rendezvous, 1989 (Box-folder 13 / 27)
  - Religious Heritage Days, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 13 / 28)
  - Requests for proposals: advertising and public relations, 1988 (Box-folder 13 / 29)
  - Requests for proposals: processing Centennial Acres deeds, 1985 (Box-folder 13 / 30)
  - Requests for proposals: video; miscellaneous, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 13 / 31)
  - Requests for proposals: video, North Country Media Group, 1989 (Box-folder 13 / 31)
  - Willard Scott visit (NBC Today Show) [photos], 1989 (Box-folder 13 / 32)
  - State and Territorial warrants (correspondence, orders, information re bounty warrants), 1985-1990 (Box-folder 13 / 33-34)
  - State telephone book (Centennial theme on cover), 1989 (Box-folder 13 / 35)
  - Students: Bozeman, Anderson School birthday cards, 1989 (Box-folder 13 / 37)
  - Students: Columbia Falls High School scrapbook (re "Echoes of the Past" play), 1989 (Box-folder 13 / 38)
  - Students: Columbus Elementary School wagon project, 1989 (Box-folder 13 / 39)
  - Students: Deer Lodge, Granville Stuart Elementary School (letters re President Bush visit), 1989 (Box-folder 13 / 40)
  - Students: East Glacier schools logo entries, 1989 (Box-folder 13 / 41)
  - Students: Florence Elementary School birthday cards and thank yous, 1989 (Box-folder 13 / 42-43)
  - Students: Fort Peck School birthday cards, 1989 (Box-folder 13 / 44)
  - Students: Glasgow, Irle School birthday cards, 1989 (Box-folder 13 / 45)
  - Students: Glendive, Washington School birthday cards, 1989 (Box-folder 13 / 46)
  - Students: Harrison School birthday cards, 1989 (Box-folder 13 / 47)
  - Students: Havre, Cottonwood School birthday cards, 1989 (Box-folder 13 / 48)
  - Students: Kremlin-Gildford Elementary School birthday cards, 1989 (Box-folder 13 / 49)
  - Students: Madison County schools birthday cards, 1989 (Box-folder OvFd / 1)
  - Students: Missoula, Hawthorne School birthday cards, 1989 (Box-folder 13 / 50)
  - Students: Oakley family birthday cards, 1989 (Box-folder 13 / 51)
  - Students: Polson Middle School RC Cola logo, 1989 (Box-folder 13 / 52)
  - Students: unidentified schools birthday cards, 1989 (Box-folder 13 / 53)
  - Students: unidentified schools birthday cards, 1989 (Box-folder 14 / 1-2)
  - Suggestions, 1982-1988 (Box-folder 14 / 3)
  - Television production on northwest region (proposed), 1985 (Box-folder 14 / 4)
  - Time capsule, 1990 (Box-folder 14 / 5)
  - Trademark registration and permission to use state seal, 1984-1987 (Box-folder 14 / 6)
  - United States Constitution bi-centennial, 1987 (Box-folder 14 / 7)
- Writings
  - "The Bright Side of Montana's Centennial", by Tom Daubert, 1988 (Box-folder 14 / 8)
  - '89ers mailing list sign-ups [scattered], 1984-1989 (Box-folder 14 / 9-10)
- Miscellany
  - Certificates of recognition issued, 1989 (Box-folder 14 / 11)
  - Licensing form letters, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 14 / 12)
  - Licensing rules and forms, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 14 / 13)
  - Lists: appreciation certificates, 1990 (Box-folder 14 / 14)
  - Lists: books, 1990 (Box-folder 14 / 15)
  - Lists: Centennial Commission members, 1985-1990 (Box-folder 14 / 16)
  - Lists: status reports on products, 1989 (Box-folder 14 / 17)
  - Lists: Montana Historical Society library and museum (items sent to), 1990 (Box-folder 14 / 18)
  - "Notable Montana Events since 1889" (compiled by Historical Research Associates), 1988 (Box-folder 14 / 19)
  - "Your Classroom and the Montana Centennial," by Larry Anderson, Helena High School, 1988 (Box-folder 14 / 20)
- Clippings
  - re "Boots and Saddles," (Bill Leininger pageant re George Armstrong Custer), 1965 (Box-folder 14 / 21)
  - Centennial Ball, 1989 (Box-folder 14 / 22)
  - Great Montana Centennial Cattle Drive, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 14 / 23-30)
  - Great Montana Centennial Cattle Drive: Meagher County News special editions, 1989 (Box-folder 14 / 31)
  - Great Montana Centennial Sheep Drive, 1989 (Box-folder 14 / 32)
  - Great Montana Centennial Swine Drive, 1989 (Box-folder 14 / 33)
  - President George Bush visit to Helena, 1989 (Box-folder 14 / 34)
  - Wagon trains, 1989 (Box-folder 14 / 35)
  - Miscellaneous (includes articles on Centennial Commission, on local events, on background, and on related topics), 1984-1989 (Box-folder 14 / 36-47)
  - Other states' celebrations, 1989 (Box-folder 14 / 48)